Guide to the John B. Duncan papers, 1932-1989 MS2055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs, 1960-1968; MS2055 Series 1; 4.5 Linear feet
  - Photograph, St. John's College, Formal Retreat, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Duncan with John Wilson, 1965 January 01 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Oath, Commission on Daycare, 1965 January 06 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, Award, Commission on Daycare, 1965 January 06 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Annual Meeting, Campfire Girls, 1965 January 11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Duncan with protesters in office, 1965 January 13 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Unknown gala, 1965 January 14 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Boxing Commissioner, 1965 January 19 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Unknown event with Lyndon B. Johnson, 1965 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Key to Gian Carlo Menotti, 1965 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, Duncan Speaking at Library dedication, 1965 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Board of Accountancy, 1965 January 26 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Award, Retired member, Board of Accountancy, 1965 January 26 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Photograph, Negro History Month Display, 1965 February (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, Unknown Awards display, 1965 February 02 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Boy Scout, 1965 February 03 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, ABC Board, 1965 February 03 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Award, Retired member of Board, 1965 February 04 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, American History Month, 1965 February 05 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Photograph, New member, Board of Barber examiner, 1965 February 05 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Photograph, License Plates, 1965 February 15 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Minimum Wage & Industrial Safety Board, 1965 March 22 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, Minimum Wage & Industrial Safety Board, 1965 March 23 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Photograph, Duncan giving letter to Campfire Girl, 1965 March 24 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Doctor's Day, 1965 March 25 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, Duncan reading "Guide to Washington for the Handicapped", 1965 April (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Photograph, Junior Commissioners Day, 1965 April 05 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, Party, "Walnut Hills", 1965 April 14 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Photograph, Board of Trustees of Library, 1965 April 15 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Photograph, Dept. of Corrections, Watergate Auditions, 1965 April 25 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Photograph, Arbor Day, Pershing Square with Lady Bird, 1965 April 30 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Petitions Presented byJr. Citizens of 2nd Precinct, 1965 May 03 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Photograph, Merit Award, Board of Public Appeals, 1965 May 04 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Oath, Board of Public Appeals, 1965 May 04 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Photograph, Duncan at National Council of Negro Women, 1965 May 06 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Commissioner Duncan presents trophies to winners of Capitol Park Bridge Tournament, 1965 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Photograph, Appointment, Board of Examiners of Veterinary Medicine, 1965 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Photograph, Star Spangled Savings Bond Luncheon, 1965 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Photograph, Oath, Redevelopment Land Agency, 1965 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Photograph, US Civil War Committee, Award to commissioners, 1965 May 12 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Photograph, Certificate of Recognition, 1965 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Photograph, Certificate of Recognition to Department of Corrections, 1965 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Traffic Safety Week, 1965 May 17 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Photograph, Proclamation of Home Rule Month, 1965 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Photograph, Proclamation of Home Rule Month, 1965 May 21 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Jack Warner (Warner Bros.), 1965 May 25 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Photograph, Commodore Dauureuther receiving award, 1965 June 04 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Photograph, Oath, Board of Optometry, 1965 June 08 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Photograph, Award, Board of Optometry, 1965 June 08 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Photograph, Duncan at DC General Hospital, 1965 June 21 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Photograph, Oath, Committee on Employment of Handicapped, 1965 June 22 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Photograph, Award, Traffic Division, 1965 June 24 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Photograph, Ceremony for WDCA-TV, 1965 June 29 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Head Start, 1965 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Photograph, Opening of Food Stamp Program, 1965 July 02 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Washington Week, 1965 July 08 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Photograph, Acceptance to Board, PWAC, 1965 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Photograph, Award, Children's' Theater Recreation Dept., 1965 July 15 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Photograph, Lyndon B. Johnson with Libby Koontz, 1965 August (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Photograph, Unknown Presentation with Duncan, 1965 August 16 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Photograph, Resolution of PKU, 1965 August 17 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Photograph, Unreadable event, written on back, 1965 August 20 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Photograph, Oath, ABC Board, 1965 August 20 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Photograph, Oath, New ABC Board member, 1965 August 25 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Photograph, Duncan with new Board member, P.W.A.B. Certificate, 1965 August 25 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Photograph, Oath, Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1965 August 26 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Photograph, Duncan at unidentified presentation, 1965 August 27 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Photograph, Duncan presenting certificate to unknown man, 1965 August 30 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Photograph, Duncan receiving check, Apprentice Council, 1965 August 31 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Photograph, Duncan receiving honorary award, 1965 September 01 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Moral Rearmament Group, 1965 September 03 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, World Law Day, 1965 September 08 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Award, Judge Bryant, 1965 September 09 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Town Crier from England, 1965 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Duncan addressing Dept. of Health and officials, 1965 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Duncan at News Conference re: Training Program, 1965 September 17 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Dorothy Goldberg Day at State Department, 1965 September 17 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Oath, Citizen Zoning Advisory Board, 1965 September 20 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, UGF Program, 1965 September 21 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner at P.T.A. Proclamation, 1965 September 21 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Denmark Week, 1965 September 23 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Volunteer Week, 1965 September 28 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Fire Prevention Week, 1965 October (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner, flag sent to Vietnam, 1965 October 08 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Civic Responsibility Week, 1965 October 12 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, United Givers Fund Campaign, 1965 October 13 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, Farewell to Lt. Cols. Adams and Wilson, 1965 October 15 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Presentation of Sunshine Bus, 1965 October 15 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Renaming of South Capital Street Bridge, 1965 October 18 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Photograph, Oath, Real Estate Commission, 1965 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Photograph, Award, Real Estate Commission, 1965 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Award, Dept. of Vocational Rehabilitation, 1965 October 28 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, Young Women's League, 1965 November (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Garden of Patriots, 1965 November 03 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, CPURAC, 1965 November 10 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, Dedication of SW Health Center, 1965 November 22 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Photograph, Dinner, Comm. of Employment of Handicapped, 1965 November 22 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Donald Brewer, Dept. Public Welfare, 1965 November 23 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Photograph, Gift given to unknown woman, 1965 November 23 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Alcoholism Information Week, 1965 December 01 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Photograph, Duncan with unknown men, 1965 December 06 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Acceptance to Apprenticeship Council, 1965 December 18 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Photograph, Oath, Council on Daycare, 1965 December 18 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Ribbon-cutting at Hine Jr. High, 1965 December 23 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Photograph, Metropolitan Police Boys Serenade, 1965 December 25 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Photograph, Award, Council on Human Relations, 1965 December 27 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Unknown Party, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - With James Washington and James Nabrit, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Duncan with FENDP Neighborhood Workers, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Duncan at UNID swearing in, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Unknown Party, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Public Welfare Advisory Council, 1966 January 18 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Acceptance of Undertakers Board, 1966 January 18 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Award, Undertakers Board, 1966 January 18 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Budget News Conference, 1966 January 24 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Rep. of Boston giving silver and hats, 1966 February 02 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Boy Scout week- pinning commissioner Duncan, 1966 February 04 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Oath, Council on Vocational Rehabilitation, 1966 February 17 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Proclamation, Foster Homes, 1966 March (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Luncheon, Morris Cafritz Hospital, 1966 March 09 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Retirement from Appeals and Review Board, 1966 May (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Oath, Board of Appeals and Review, 1966 May (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Dinner, 1966 May (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Public Health Advisory Council, 1966 May 09 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Swearing In, Public Health Advisory Council, 1966 May 09 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Savings Bond Drive, 1966 May 18 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Duncan, Tobriner and Mayor of Germany, 1966 May 19 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Proclamation, Youth Opportunity Night, 1966 May 24 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Appointment, Public Welfare Advisory Board, 1966 May 24 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Duncan and Governor Tamrant, 1966 June 17 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Duncan, Tobriner, Foreign Min. of Togo, 1966 July 06 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Visiting Children's Convalescent Hospital, 1966 July 06 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Swearing In, Recreation Board, 1966 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Award, Retirement from Recreation Board, 1966 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Award, retirement from Public Welfare Advisory Council, 1966 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Swearing In, Public welfare Advisory Council, 1966 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Swearing In, Board of Pharmacy, 1966 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Award, Retirement, 1966 July 20 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Big Brothers Picnic, 1966 July 23 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Oath, Advisory Council on Fire Prevention, 1966 August 09 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Oath, Board of Appeals and Review, 1966 August 09 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Swearing In, Board of Cosmetology, 1966 August 17 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - retirement, Board of Cosmetology, 1966 August 17 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Emergency Family Shelter, 1966 August 24 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - 100th Anniversary of Howard University, 1966 September 16 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Gift to Government of Somalia, 1966 September 23 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Award, Retirement from Real Estate Commission, 1966 October 04 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Swearing In, Real Estate Commission, 1966 October 04 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Proclamation, Civic Responsibility Week, 1966 October 11 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Proclamation, Tire Safety Week, 1966 October 11 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Proclamation, Patriotic Education Week, 1966 October 11 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Duncan with Matsuda and Ferrer, 1966 October 13 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - New member, Public Welfare Council, 1966 October 14 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Proclamation, Business Women's Week, 1966 October 17 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Queens of National Flower Week, 1966 October 19 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - 14th Annual DC Award, 1966 October 21 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Award, Board of Podiatry, 1966 October 24 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Swearing In, Board of Podiatry, 1966 October 24 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - New member, Board of Podiatry, 1966 October 24 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Vocational Guidance Week, 1966 October 27 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dedication F Street Plaza, 1966 November 01 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Interdenominational Church Ushers Assn, 1966 November 01 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Diabetes Detection Week, 1966 November 02 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - League of Women Voters Week, 1966 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Signing the transit compact, 1966 November 22 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Award, DC driver for driver ed participation, 1966 December 06 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Photograph, Minimum Wage and Ind. Safety Board, 1967 January 17 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, Washington Bible Society presentation, 1967 January 17 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Award, Retirement from Board of Library Trustees, 1967 January 30 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Award, Retirement from Board of Dental Examiners, 1967 January 30 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Board of Dental Examiners, 1967 January 30 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Children's Dental Health Week, 1967 January 30 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Commission on Status of Women, 1967 February 13 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Negro History Week, 1967 February 09 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Mrs. Edward Boehm, 1967 February 27 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Community Renewal Program Presentation, 1967 March 14 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Award, Retirement from Board of Library Trustees, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Board of Library Trustees, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Award, Retirement, Phys. Therapists Examining Board, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Phys. Therapists Exam. Board, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Photograph, Award, Retirement from Board of Optometry, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Board of Optometry, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, Board of Cosmetology, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, Board of Examiners in Vet. Medicine, 1967 April 14 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Drew Elementary School, 1967 April 25 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Schuyler Lowe retirement party, 1967 May (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Photograph, Child Care Day Proclamation, 1967 May 01 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Cerebral Palsy Month, 1967 May 02 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner, front District Building, 1967 May 03 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, Public Health Advisory Council, 1967 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Photograph, Award, Public Health Advisory Council, 1967 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Appointment, Board of Accountancy, 1967 May 17 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, Duncan, Tobriner and Mathe, 1967 May 19 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Thailand Governors, 1967 May 26 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, Dedication of four pools, 1967 June 07 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Photograph, Award, Citizen Traffic Board, 1967 June 20 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Photograph, New member, Citizen Traffic Board, 1967 June 20 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Photograph, Council for Youth, 1967 June 22 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Russian Women, 1967 June 29 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Photograph, Col. Reynolds' Departure, 1967 July 07 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Duncan's Asst., William Van Dyke, 1967 July 11 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Photograph, Appointment to Board of Optometry, 1967 July 12 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Photograph, Award to Dr. Paul Hoffman, 1967 July 12 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Photograph, Safety Award to Duncan, 1967 July 17 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Photograph, Swearing In, 1967 July 21 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Photograph, Meeting, 1967 July 26 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Walter Washington, John Conyers, 1967 September (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Photograph, Award, Amy Hunt and Duncan [1968?], 1967 September 20 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Natl Employ. of Handicapped Week, 1967 September 28 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Fire Prevention Week, 1967 October (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Photograph, Georgetown Historic District, 1967 October 07 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Photograph, Duncan receiving award at USO, Circa 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Photograph, New member, ABC Board, 1968 March 04 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Photograph, Bob McConnell's Farewell Party, 1969 February (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Photograph, Self-Esteem Program, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Photograph, Dinner with men, one in African dress, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Photograph, Certificate, United Givers' Fund, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Photograph, Duncan and JFK shaking hands with boy, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Hotel La Concha, Puerto Rico, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, Women on donkey, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Photograph, Sorority Presenting Scroll to Duncan, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Photograph, Duncan with girls' class and nuns, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Photograph, School Portrait of Boy, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Photograph, Duncan with man, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Gala at Sheraton-Park Hotel, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Photograph, Duncan with three other men, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Photograph, Lena B. Duncan with Libby Koontz, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Ambassadors from Mali, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Photograph, Photo trick, same man at 5 places, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking at Willard, undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking at Board of Trading Meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two men at table, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Photograph, Autographed, Duncan with E. Dinga, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Photograph, Duncan in group with Johnny Carson at Gala, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Gala, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Photograph, Duncan shaking hands with man at Gala, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Photograph, Abandoned Cars, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Photograph, Retiring Board Members, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Photograph, Fire Prevention Week, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Photograph, With Hubert Humphrey, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Photograph, Cafritz Hospital, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Photograph, Duncan next to speaker, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner, Key to Kirk Douglas and other man, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Photograph, Contact sheets of party, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Photograph, Duncan receiving award from Baptist Conference, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Duncan with woman and man, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Photograph, Duncan shaking hands with man, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Photograph, Unidentified Party, undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Photograph, Unidentified Presentation, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner with two unidentified men, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Photograph, Duncan and two women at party, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Photograph, Duncan, two men and clergyman, undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Mayflower Hotel with Lyndon B. Johnson, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Photograph, Meeting with Lyndon B. Johnson, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Photograph, Duncan at unidentified party, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Photograph, Unidentified event, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Photograph, Unidentified meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Photograph, Ceremony at Lincoln Memorial, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Photograph, Crowning Queen, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Photograph, Duncan receiving award at Sheraton, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Photograph, Duncan with woman in African dress and man, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Photograph, Outdoor Picnic, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Photograph, Graduation Ceremony, undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Photograph, Duncan and wife at party, undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Photograph, View from 2nd floor Brackett Hall, Potomac River, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Photograph, Duncan with group, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Photograph, With Commissioners, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Photograph, Duncan and group with Lyndon B. and Lady Bird Johnson, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Photograph, Duncan at Livingstone College ceremony, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Photograph, Duncan with group of men touring milk plant, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Photograph, Duncan, Tobriner and two others sipping tea, undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Miss Fire Prevention, undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Photograph, Duncan at unidentified dinner, undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Photograph, Duncan with two women, undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking at Mayflower Hotel, undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Photograph, Duncan with Bitwoded Ras, Andargachew Mesaye, undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Photograph, Bus keys given to junior Village, undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Photograph, Duncan with four men, undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Photograph, Duncan, Tobriner giving award to Robert Martin, undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Photograph, Duncan giving key to city to man, undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner watching speaker, undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Photograph, Duncan, Tobriner with three men, undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Photograph, Group at airport with President of Sudan, undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Photograph, Duncan and wife with couple at party, undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Photograph, Duncan and wife with three others at party, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Photograph, Meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Photograph, Duncan with three unidentified men and boy, undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Photograph, Proclamation of Appreciation, Robert Byrd, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Photograph, Duncan receiving plaque from group, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Photograph, Group, Of meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Photograph, Award, Glendale Hospital, Train Wreck Work, undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner with unidentified man and woman in African dress, undated (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner give key, undated (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Photograph, World Health Day, Smallpox Vaccine Drive, undated (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Photograph, Unknown Dinner, undated (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Tobriner with unknown man with booklet, undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Photograph, Duncan and Gershon Fishbein, undated (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Photograph, Proclamation, Volunteer Week, undated (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Photograph, Certificate of Outstanding Performance, undated (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Photograph, Duncan speaking at meeting, undated (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Photograph, Hubert Humphrey speaking at Civil Air Patrol, undated (Box 8, Folder 90)